Y'all know what the pink jacket mean, right?
Y'all know what the Afro getting picked out means, right?
It means it's time for another In a Man That We Trust screening.
How many members are there?
Because I'm going to keep it present tense.
Okay.
In the Migos.
Three.
Do you know how many members of Destiny's Child there are?
Well, it depends on what era.
So I'll take that as a yes.
Yes.
Okay.
How many senators are there?
That's a lot of them.
That's right, DC.
Me, my pink suit, and my Afro.
I'm coming to your town October 7th for the Because They're Funny Festival.
I'm going to be doing political trivia, handing out free stuff, doing stand-up.
We're going to screen the documentary, and we're going to do a Q&A.
That's a whole lot.
We're going to be at the wharf at Union Stage, 1 p.m.
Get your tickets at BecauseThey'reFunny.com, at AmandaSeals.com, or right here at my link
in bio.
See you there.